1. openBrowser("")
7. Navigating to our base url.
13. Waiting for the "Make Appointment" button to visible.
19. Clicking on the "Make Appointment" button.
25. Adding "John Doe" as username.
31. Adding password for the user.
37. Verifying that login button is clickable or not ?
43. Clicking on login button.
49. Selecting value from the dropdown box.
55. Checking checkbox.
61. Selecting radio button.
67. Clicking on calender icon.
73. Clicking on "22" text.(Date)
79. Adding text into description text area.
85. Verifying that "Book Appointment"  button is clickable or not ?
91. Clicking on "Book Appointment" button.
97. Verfying text after clicking on "Book Appointment" button.
103. Verifying "Go to Homepage" button is visible or not.
109. Verifying "Go to Homepage" button is clickable or not.
115. Clicking on "Go to Homepage" button.
121. Waiting for the element of home page to be visible.
127. Verifying text from the home page.
133. Closing browser.